Spiros Xiarchos

Information Systems Specialist

Email:
Web: xiarchos.gr

About Me

Hey there, I'm Spyros and I am a senior student in the Department of Informatics of the Ionian University. During my studies I gained a wide experience in the following fields:

- · Constructive wireless networks
- · Hardware maintenance and repairing
- · E-shop creation
- · Website creation

On top of the technical skills that were built throughout my experience in several companies, I consider myself as a great team player and strong analytical thinker.

Education

B.Sc. Informatics

Ionian University, GR

10/2015 - Present

Specialization in Information Systems.

Main courses follow:

- Strategy & Management of Information Systems
- Analysis & Design of Information Systems
- · Information Systems & Supply Chain
- Electronic Commerce

Experience

Web and Sound Services Freelancer

Freelance

09/2019 - Present

- Web Site Creation and Development
- E-Shop Creation and Development
- Sound Design and Mix

Hardware Maintainance and Repairing Assistant

Spyretos Computer Service and Repair, Corfu GR

08/2018 - 08/2019

- Hardware Repairing & Maintenance
- IT Technical Support
- Customer Care Services

Network Expansion Assistant

MNET, Kalamata GR

11/2015 - 08/2018

- Wireless Link Expansion and Maintenance
- IT Tech Support

A Little More About Me

Apart from the job related interests I'm keen on:

- Tech Savvy
- Vinyl Record Collection
- Music Production
- MotoGP Fan

Spiros Xiarchos -